<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<extensionAdditionalInfo>
  <info><![CDATA[
    <p>
	  The Axosoft extension provides issue tracking integration with Axosoft
	  OnTime 10 and later.
	</p>
	<h3>Prerequisites</h3>
	<p>
	  You must have an OnTime server configured and working on your network, and
	  the OnTime SDK installed and properly configured to allow remote web service
	  calls.
	</p>
	<h3>Generating a Security Token</h3>
	<p>
	  If you have not already done so, you will need to generate a Security Token for OnTime.
	  Open the web.config file in the root folder of wherever you have installed the OnTime SDK,
	  and find the &lt;appSettings&gt; section. In this section, you should see a SecurityToken key:
	</p>
    <blockquote style="font-family: Consolas, 'Courier New', courier;">
      &lt;add key="SecurityToken" value="SECURITY-TOKEN-GUID"/&gt;
	</blockquote>
	<p>
	  You will need to generate a GUID to use as the security token. When pasting it, make sure
	  you don't include the {} characters. Also note that this element is commented out by default;
	  make sure you uncomment it.
	</p>
	<h3>Creating an Issue Tracking Provider in BuildMaster</h3>
	<p>
	  Now you are ready to create an OnTime Issue Tracking Provider in BuildMaster. When adding
	  the provider, you will be presented with some OnTime-specific configuration options:
	</p>
	<img src="/resources/images/extensions/ontime-provider.png" alt="OnTime Provider" title="OnTime Provider" />
	<p>
	  You must specify the OnTime web service URL and the security token. The web service URL is
	  simply the root virtual directory where the OnTime SDK web service has been installed in IIS
	  on your OnTime server. The security token is the GUID that was added to the OnTime SDK's
	  web.config file.
	</p>
	<p>
	  The OnTime Web URL field is optional – it is simply the URL of OnTime's web interface which
	  BuildMaster will use to hyperlink OnTime defect and features.
	</p>
	<p>
	  If everything has been configured properly, clicking Test Connection should display a connection
	  successful indicator. If there is a problem reaching the web service, verify that the web service
	  URL is correct by pointing to it with your browser or checking out the IIS administration console
	  on your OnTime server.
	</p>
  ]]></info>
</extensionAdditionalInfo>