<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<extensionAdditionalInfo>
  <info><![CDATA[
  <p> This extension contains actions for getting dependencies from <a href="http://nuget.org">NuGet</a>, creating a NuGet package, and publishing packages to NuGet. </p>
  ]]></info>
  <actionInfo id="Inedo.BuildMasterExtensions.NuGet.SetReleaseNotes" name="Set Release Notes" summary="Writes release notes to a .nuspec file using BuildMaster's release notes or the Application's issue tracker."><![CDATA[
  <h3>Action Fields</h3>
  <h4>Release Notes Source</h4>
  <p>Select whether to generate release notes from BuildMaster's Application Release Notes, the Application's associated Issue Tracker, or both.</p>
  <h4>Nuspec File</h4>
  <p>The name of the .nuspec file where the release notes will be written to. This file name is relative to the source directory.</p>
  ]]></actionInfo>
  <actionInfo id="Inedo.BuildMasterExtensions.NuGet.PushPackage" name="Publish NuGet Package" summary="Publishes a package using NuGet."><![CDATA[
  <h3>Action Fields</h3>
  <h4>Package</h4>
  <p>Package to publish using NuGet. If a relative path is used, it is relative to the source directory.</p>
  <h4>Server Configuration</h4>
  <p>The API Key and server URL used to publish the package.</p>
  ]]></actionInfo>
  <actionInfo id="Inedo.BuildMasterExtensions.NuGet.CreatePackage" name="Create NuGet Package" summary="Creates a package using NuGet."><![CDATA[
  <h3>Action Fields</h3>
  <h4>Project or Nuspec</h4>
  <p>Provide the nuspec file or msbuild project file that will act as the source of the NuGet package. If a relative path is used, it is relative to the source path.</p>
  <h4>Version</h4>
  <p>Specify a version for the NuGet package. If not specified, the version in the nuspec file will be used.</p>
  <h4>Properties</h4>
  <p>Provide additional properties to pass to NuGet. Use the format Property=Value (one per line). For example:<br />
<i>Configuration=Release</i></p>
  <h4>Options</h4>
  <p>Additional options for controlling package creation such as verbose logging, whether to include symbols in the package, and if the project should be built. </p>
  ]]></actionInfo>
  <actionInfo id="Inedo.BuildMasterExtensions.NuGet.InstallPackages" name="Install NuGet Packages" summary="Installs NuGet packages specified by a packages.config file."><![CDATA[
  <h3>Action Fields</h3>
  <h4>Package Source</h4>
  <p>Provide the URL of the package source. If not specified, all sources in %AppData%\NuGet\NuGet.config are used.</p>
  <h4>Packages</h4>
  <p>Provide the location of the packages.config file. If a relative path is used, it is relative to the source path.</p>
  ]]></actionInfo>
</extensionAdditionalInfo>